I just saw Kathy naked.
방금 캐시의 알몸을 봤어
이건 고문이야
It was like torture.
If we go to war and you're captured,
you're in for a surprise.
네가 전쟁포로가 된다면
경악할 일이 벌어지겠다?
It keeps getting worse.
갈수록 태산이야, 룸메이트의
여자친구를 사랑하게 됐는데
It bad enough that I'm in love
with my roommate's girlfriend.
캐시도 알고 있는 것 같아
Every time we're in the same room,
there's weird energy between us.
셋이 함께 있으면
분위기가 야릇해지니까
Call me crazy, but
I think she likes me too.
미쳤다고 해도 좋지만
짝사랑은 아닐 거야
And now I have seen her naked.
이제 알몸까지 봤어
At least with her clothes on...
지금까진 온몸에 부스럼이
났을 거라고 위안을 삼았는데
...I could imagine her body
was covered in boils.
But there are no boils.
She's smooth.
부스럼은 없었어
매끈하더라고
Smooth!
매끈해!
와, 가운 사이로
뭐가 보이더라
-Could everyone see up his robe?
-Oh, my God!
The One Where
Chandler Crosses the Line
-Here you go.
-I'll call you.
- 여기 있어요
- 네, 전화할게요
Great!
그래요
Hey, hey. Who was that?
이봐, 저 여잔 누구야?
Casey. We're going out tonight.
케이시라고 하는데
오늘밤에 만날 거야
Going out? Wow!
만난다고? 와우!
그럼 캐시하곤 깨진 거냐?
It didn't work out
with Kathy? Bummer.
No, things are fine.
그쪽도 이상 없어
I'm having a late meal with her
after an early one with Casey.
늦은 저녁엔 캐시랑 먹을 거고
초저녁엔 케이시랑 먹을 거야
-What?
-Yeah.
뭐?
그런데도 방금 피자 한 판을
먹어치웠다는 게 놀랍지?
The craziest thing is,
I just ate a whole pizza myself.
야, 넌 캐시랑 사귀잖아
You're going out with Kathy!
Yeah. Why are you upset?
- 근데 왜 열을 내고 그래
- 그건... 걱정돼서지
Well, I'm upset...
...for you.
예쁜 여자들을 줄줄이 꿰차도
마음 한 귀퉁이가 허전하냐?
Sex with an endless line of beautiful
women must be unfulfilling.
What's the big deal?
It's not like we're exclusive.
뭐 어때, 서로 얽매인
사이도 아닌데
Look, Joey.
조이
Kathy's clearly not fulfilling
your emotional needs.
캐시는 네 마음을
채워줄 수 없나 보다
하지만 케이시는...
물론 난 뒤통수만 봤지만
But, Casey....
Granted, I just saw
the back of her head.
똑똑하고 재미있고
널 사로잡았다는 필이 와
But I got this sense
that she's smart and funny...
...and gets you.
You got all that
from the back of her head?
뒤통수에 그렇게 적혔어?
I think it's time
for you to settle down.
너도 이제 안정을 찾아야지
선택을 해, 하나를 고르라고
Make a choice.
Pick a lane.
Who's Elaine?
'하나'는 또 누군데
Little Tony Tarzan
꼬마 타잔 토니가
코털을 잡고 흔들리네
Swinging on a nose hair
Swinging with the greatest of ease
I don't know the next verse.
다음은 어떻게 가지?
You could just go:
이건 어때
Greatest of ease
흔들리네, 밤마나마나마
거기서 바로 들어가
Then go right into it.
I like that.
그거 좋다
How do you know about...?
근데 밤마나마나마를
어떻게 생각해냈어?
You know, I used to play.
- 나도 악기 좀 다뤘잖아
- 맞아, 키보드였지?
That's right.
The keyboards?
그래, 고등학교 때 시작해서
대학 가서는 푹 빠져버렸어
A little in high school.
I got into it in college.
그때 내 음악성을 발견했지
That's when
I really found my sound.
Orange juice just came out
of my nose, but it was worth it.
이런, 주스가 코로 나와도
이상할 게 없지?
Oh, my God!
세상에, 오빠 음악성을
잊고 있었네?
I completely forgot about
your sound.
그래
He'd lock himself in
the basement for hours.
지하실에 내려가서
몇 시간씩 연습했는데
No one was ever allowed to hear
the sound.
아무도 그 소리를
들을 수 없었지
I want to hear the sound.
난 그 소리 듣고 싶어
No, I mean,
I haven't played in so long.
안돼, 너무 오래 전 일이야
Well, it's really personal stuff.
나만을 위한 음악이거든
Play that funky music, white boy.
그 펑키한 음악 좀 들어보자
-Yeah, come on.
-No, you guys.
어서 해봐
안된다니까, 키보드도 저기...
그래, 알았어
My keyboards are all the way
Yeah, okay.
Who wants to get dinner later?
I wanna try that new ltalian restaurant.
나랑 저녁 먹을 사람?
근사한 이태리 식당인데
Supposed to be really good. Saw a
lot of Chinese people eating in there.
굉장히 맛있나 봐
중국인 손님들이 많거든
What are you talking about?
무슨 소리야
You said some restaurant must be good
because Chinese people were eating there.
중국인들이 많이 오면
괜찮은 레스토랑이라며
That's because it was
a Chinese restaurant.
거긴 중국집이었으니까
I still wanna go.
Who wants to come?
그래도 갈래
누구 없어?
Oh, I can't. I got two dinner dates
tonight, so I gotta get ready.
난 안돼, 오늘 데이트
두 탕이나 뛰어야 돼
준비하러 간다
All right, girls' night out.
처녀들의 저녁식사네?
Sorry, but we have to prep that
catering thing for tomorrow.
미안하지만 내일
출장요리가 있어
Oh, that's right.
그렇구나
I wish I could eat
in restaurants alone.
- 혼자 외식하긴 뭐하고
- 해봐, 얼마나 좋은데
You should try it.
It's a really good thing to do.
I just think I'd feel really self-conscious.
Like I was on display or something.
왠지 불편해서 싫어
구경거리 되는 것 같잖아
I was on display once.
Nothing like eating alone.
난 구경거리 돼봤는데
혼자 먹는 게 양반이다
I just had a great time with myself.
홀로 즐거운 시간이었어
Well, this could be a good story.
재미나는 스토리겠다?
At dinner.
It was so liberating.
저녁 먹었네요
얼마나 편하고 좋던지
난 혼자서도 잘 노는 애야!
You know, I don't need people to
have fun. I'm fun. I'm a fun girl.
Are you a naughty girl?
왜 아랫도리가 저리냐?
No, just fun. Fun. Good. Fun.
아! 그렇게 잘 논다고?
- 좋을 거라고 했지?
- 맞아
-See, I told you you'd have fun.
-I know.
Although I must say that I totally
judge any woman I see eating alone.
난 혼자 식사하는 여자
좋게 안 보이더라
-Why?
-What's wrong with a woman eating alone?
왜
혼자 먹는 여자가
어디가 어때서
여자가 혼자 먹잖아
Well, obviously something.
She's eating alone.
Okay, guys.
- 됐다, 얘들아
- 그래, 풍악을 울려라
All right! Bring it on, you!
Here we go.
갑니다
You know, I've never played
my stuff for anyone before.
미리 말해두지만 남 앞에서
연주한 적은 한 번도 없어
So it's important that
you understand...
매우 사적인 감정이라는 걸
전제로 하고 감상하길 바래
...it's about communicating...
...very private emotions.
You know....
그러니까... 내 작품은 말없는
소리의 시라는 걸 명심하고
You should think of my work...
...as wordless sound poems.
-That's what
-Oh, my God, play.
- 다시 말해...
- 빨랑 두들겨!
Well, you know, that was...
이건 정말...
...terrific!
경악스럽다!
Really...
진짜... 사람 잡는 걸?
...bitchen.
Wow! It was so wow!
와우!
말 그대로... 와우다!
Really?
정말이야?
Yeah! I mean, you should
play in public.
그래, 썩히기 아까운 재주야
Wow, thanks, you guys.
That's
정말 고맙다
하나 더 들려줄게
I want to play you another piece.
I left my helicopter sounds on
another disk. I'll be right back, okay?
헬리콥터 사운드는 다른
디스크에 있어, 금방 올게
이건 정말 감격이다
난 너무...
This is so nice.
I mean, I am so....
God bless my dad for
soundproofing the basement.
다행히 아빠가 지하실에
방음장치를 했지 뭐야
I can't believe I ever let him
touch me with those fingers.
그 손가락으로
날 만졌다니
무슨 소리야?
근사하잖아
What are you guys talking about?
I loved it!
It was so moving.
너무 감동적이다
이건 평범한 음악이 아냐
It's so different
from the stuff you usually hear.
You mean, music?
음악이 아니니까
무슨 생각하는지 안다
I know what you think.
Yes, yes, your breasts
are just as firm and juicy.
그래, 네 가슴도
탱탱하고 촉촉해
Come in.
들어와요
나예요, 이런 세상에
그거 '베이 워치'예요?
Oh, God! Is that Baywatch?
Yes, but I just watch it
for the articles.
네, 연구 목적이죠
-So is Joey around?
-No, he's not back yet.
조이 있어요?
아뇨, 외출 중인데
금방 올 거예요
와서 앉아요
이물? 고물?
Come in, have a seat.
Bow or stern?
I don't have a preference. You?
- 아무 데나 좋아요, 당신은?
- 전 뒤쪽을 선호하죠
I like it in the stern.
Of the boat.
물론 보트에서
여보세요
It's me. Casey and l
had a little car trouble.
나야, 돌아가는 길인데
차에 문제가 좀 생겼어
-What happened?
-We broke down.
무슨 일인데?
도로에서 멈춰버렸지 뭐야
미션 오일을 구해와야겠어
I have to get transmission fluid.
Tell Kathy that I'm sorry
and I'll be there soon.
캐시한테 곧 간다고
말 좀 잘 전해 줘
-Why can't you tell her?
-I think my time is about to
직접 얘기하지 그래
동전을 하나밖에
안 넣어서...
- 조이? 조이?
- 그래
I thought your time ran out.
끊긴 줄 알았잖아
Me too, but I guess I do have
나도 그런 줄 알았는데...
Joey's running a little late,
and he says he's sorry.
조이가 좀 늦을 거라고
미안하다네요
둘만 있게 됐군요
I guess it's just you and me, then.
-Okay.
-Yeah, I think it is.
- 좋아요
- 사실이 그래요
So, what'd you do today?
오늘 뭐했어요?
I had an appointment
to cut my hair.
- 이발소에 예약을 했는데
- 멋진데요?
-Looks great!
-And then it got canceled.
근데 취소됐어요
-I could cut it.
-Really? Do you do that?
나도 자를 수 있는데
- 정말 할 줄 알아요?
- 그럼요
Yeah, I learned at my aunt's
dog-grooming shop. What do you say?
이모네 애견미용실에서
배웠는데 괜찮겠죠?
Dog grooming?
애견미용실?
Don't make my tail too poofy.
그럼, 꼬리는 너무 살리지 말고
You have really great hair.
머릿결이 참 좋아요
Oh, thanks. I grow it myself.
고마워요, 직접 기른 건데
You know who also
has great hair is Joey.
- 조이 머릿결도 좋죠
- 네, 맞아요
Yes, Joey has great hair.
I'm basically done here.
Let me get this hair off your neck.
대충 끝난 것 같네요
머리카락 좀 털어내고
What are you doing?
뭐하는 거죠?
Checking to see if it's even.
길이가 맞나 보려구요
네
Looks good.
괜찮네요
The phone!
The phone's making sounds!
전화통이 울린다!
- 여보세요?
- 나야
Hey, dude, it's me.
Hey, it's Joey!
조이예요
당분간 못 움직일 것 같아
오일은 구했는데 변속기가 없어
It looks like we'll be stuck here.
I got the fluid.
The transmission wasn't there.
-What?
-It fell out.
뭐?
아까 개를 칠 때
떨어져 나갔나 봐
I just figured we hit a dog.
알았어
Could you put Kathy on?
I want to apologize to her.
캐시한테 직접
사과해야겠어
그래
받아 봐요
It's Joey.
나야, 괜찮아
걱정하지 마
No, it's fine.
Don't worry about it.
Yeah, no, stop apologizing.
It's okay.
사과할 필요 없다니까
I'll talk to you tomorrow.
그래, 내일 얘기해
I should probably go.
- 가봐야겠어요
- 네, 그래요
I forgot my purse.
지갑을 깜빡했네요
I really did.
I forgot my purse.
지갑을 두고 갔어요
- 안돼, 이건 아냐
- 끔찍해요
-This is bad! It's bad!
-Horrible!
Wait, the kiss or the situation?
잠깐, 키스가?
이 상황이?
The kiss was good.
아니, 키스는 좋았어요
-But that's bad!
-Here's what we do.
- 하지만 안돼요!
- 네, 이렇게 하죠
-We forget it happened.
-What?
- 없었던 일로 쳐요
- 네?
감정을 정리합시다, 평생
불행해진대도, 훌륭하죠?
We swallow our feelings, even if
we're unhappy forever. Sound good?
Can you really do that?
정말 그럴 수 있어요?
I have to. He's my best friend.
그럼 어떡해요
둘도 없는 친구의 연인인 걸
And you're seeing him.
챈들러? 난 조이가 좋지만
당신과 있으면...
Chandler, I like Joey a lot.
-But with you
-No, don't! Don't, see?
시작하지 말아요
You're getting me confused.
I'm starting to yearn.
이렇게 나오면 나 망가져요
I'm sorry.
미안해요
If you want to pretend that
nothing happened, I can try.
없었던 일로 치고 싶다면
나도 노력할게요
I think we have to.
그래야 해요
알았어요
- 안녕
- 잘 가요
Are you still out there?
- 아직 거기 있어요?
- 아뇨
Electrifying
전기 쇼크
Infinite time
무한한 시간
There's a Starbucks
about three blocks down.
세 블록 밑에
스타벅스가 있어
He's so inspired.
Just look at him. Look at him go!
영감을 받아 전율하는
저 모습을 보란 말야!
Thank you very much!
대단히 감사합니다
Hey, aren't you up next?
올라가야지?
-I'm not playing tonight.
-Why not?
- 아니, 오늘은 쉴래
- 왜?
I can't follow Ross.
로스랑 비교되잖아
It'd be like those
poor bicycle-riding chimps...
비틀즈 흉내내는 원숭이가
될 순 없어, 안되지!
...who had to
follow the Beatles. No.
피비, 오빠는 꽝이야
Ross sucks.
The place has emptied because of him.
덕분에 가게 파리만 날리잖아
Oh, my God, he's not even
appreciated in his own time.
맙소사, 이 시대가
천재를 버리는구나
I'd give anything to not be
appreciated in my own time!
나도 시대의 버림을 받고 싶어
좋아, 피비?
You suck too.
너도 꽝이야
피비, 넌...
You're awful.
폭탄이야
얘들아...
You guys!
니들도 꽝이다
You suck too!
Man! I can't believe
I locked myself out again!
돌겠군, 또 문을
잠그고 나갔어!
잠깐 기다려
Hang on, buddy.
Oh, my God! What happened?
세상에, 이게 뭐지?
네가 산 거야?
-Did you do all this? Why?
-I sure did.
- 물론이지
- 왜?
It made me feel good to do
something nice for my friend.
친구의 기쁨이 곧
나의 기쁨이니까
You're amazing.
- 너 대단하다?
- 아니, 이게 대단하지
No, this is amazing.
A TV that appears
as if from nowhere!
TV가 난데없이 출현하네?
That's the dream!
이건 꿈이야
How did you afford all this?
돈이 어디서 났어?
I'm 29. I mean, who needs
a savings account?
나이 스물 아홉에
통장이 왜 필요해?
You're the best friend
anyone has ever had.
- 너 같은 친구는 없을 거야
- 글쎄다
I don't know.
No, you are.
맞아, 이것도 물론이려니와
내 듬직한 조언자 아냐
You do this, you give me advice....
What you said about
focusing on one woman?
그리고 어제 한 여자만
확실히 잡으라고 했지?
I'll do that.
- 그렇게 할 거야
- 케이시를?
With Casey?
아니, 아무리 생각해도
캐시만한 여자는 없어
I'll see how things go with Kathy.
She's cool.
-Or Casey.
-No, Kathy.
- 케이시도?
- 아냐, 캐시
-Could be Casey.
-No, Kathy.
- 케이시도 좋잖아?
- 아니, 캐시야
케이시 쪽도 밀어봐
Consider Casey.
I think somebody's
got a little crush on Casey.
너 케이시가 맘에 있구나
내가 다리 한 번 놔봐?
I'll fix you two up.
What do you think?
That all the pieces of my life
are falling right into place.
드디어 내 인생에도
서광이 비치는도다!
- 너 정말 타고났다
- 고마워
You were really great.
You were really, really great.
Thanks.
Monica tells me you don't want
to play anymore because of me...
모니카가 그러는데
이제 노래 안 한다며?
내 천부적인 재능 때문에
...and, you know, my talent.
Is that true?
진짜야?
- 그런 것 같아
- 피비...
Well, kind of, yeah.
I was trying to be really okay
and upbeat about it...
그냥 잊어버리려고 해도
...but I just feel so dwarfed
by your musical gift.
네 천재적인 음악성에는
짓눌릴 수밖에 없더라
See, but....
하지만 내 음악의 취지는
절대 그런 게 아니거든
Pheebs, that is the exact
opposite intent of my music.
You know, my music
is meant to inspire.
내 음악의 주제는
영감의 자극이야
If it bothers you this much...
그렇게 부담스럽다면...
...then I won't play anymore.
연주에서 손떼겠어
No, don't do that.
안돼, 그러지 마
How could I live if I knew I was
depriving the world of your music?
한 천재의 음악성을
망가뜨려서야 쓰나
Yeah, okay.
그래, 알았어
-I'd love to, but I have plans on Sunday.
-Well, maybe some other time.
- 일요일엔 다른 계획이 있어요
- 그럼 다음 기회에
-Sure. Just give me a call, I'm in the book.
-Okay. Thanks a lot. See you.
좋아요, 전화하세요
네, 고마워요
또 보죠
커험!
What are you doing?
He is cute, and he's a doctor.
무슨 짓이야?
잘생긴 의사한테
-How do you know?
-Honey, I eavesdrop because I care.
- 어떻게 알아?
- 난 관심 있는 건 엿들어
-Well, I have plans on Sunday.
-With who?
- 일요일엔 약속이 있어
- 누구하고?
-Me.
-Oh, God.
- 나랑!
- 어머나
혼자 보내는 시간이
중요하다고 한 게 누군데
You are the one who told me how
important it is to spend time alone.
I can't just go out with that guy
when I have plans with myself.
계획을 포기하고 저 남자를
만나면 나에 대한 배신행위지
Wouldn't be fair to me.
So basically you're saying you
don't want to cheat on yourself.
널 두고 바람피울 수 없다?
Well, if you wanna make
me sound crazy.
그렇다고 하면
미친 여자겠지?
Saw the new furniture. Very nice.
새로 들인 가구
참 근사하더라
조이는 멋진 남자친구가
있어서 너무 좋겠다
Joey has the best boyfriend ever!
I kissed Kathy.
캐시랑 키스했어
- 맙소사
- 정말이야?
Are you serious?
조이도 알아?
-Does Joey know?
-No.
아니, 그 녀석이
이해할 수 있을까?
Is there any way you think
he will understand this?
You obviously haven't
screwed over your friends.
친구 물먹인 적이
별로 없구나
Which we all appreciate.
다행한 일이야
If you'd told him how you felt
before you kissed her...
사전에 솔직하게 털어놨으면
조이가 물러설 수도 있었잖아
...knowing Joey,
he'd have stepped aside.
Don't say that!
That's not true, is it?
그런 말하지 마
절대 아니지?
- 그랬을 거야
- 우정을 위해
Yeah, he loves you.
Then why didn't you
tell me to do that?
그럼 진작 그러라고 하지!
I said something to Phoebe.
- 피비한테는 얘기했는데
- 아주 좋은 생각이었어
And I thought it was
a really good idea.
-Yeah, I remember.
-Oh, my God!
- 그래, 나도 기억나
- 미치겠네
어떡하지?
What am I going to do?
- 조이한테 얘기해
- 왜, 내가 왜 해?
-You'll have to tell him.
-Why do I have to tell him?
-Because you do.
-Yeah, I know.
- 말할 거잖아
- 그렇지
저기... 이걸 소재로
곡 하나 써도 되니?
Would it be okay
if I wrote a song about this?
I don't know if this is
working out. I think....
이게 잘될까?
아무래도 다른 사람을
만나고 싶은가 보다
I think I wanna see other people.
Wow. Didn't see that coming.
현재로선 가망이 없구나
It's not that I don't
enjoy this. I do.
물론 이것도 즐겁지만
다른 세상을 경험하고 싶다
I just wanna see
what else is out there.
Hey, Guy. What are you doing here?
안녕하세요
여긴 웬일로
I work across the street.
건너편이 저희 병원이에요
알고 보니 이번 주엔
약속이 없었어요
-lt turns out I'm gonna be free Sunday.
-I wish you had called me.
전화하지 그랬어요
근무스케줄 잡아버렸는데
I just told them I'd work this weekend.
Okay, well, maybe next weekend.
그럼 다음주는 어때요?
-Definitely. I'll see you.
-Okay.
- 좋죠, 그때 봐요
- 그래요
Yeah, you'll be talking to me never,
because you're a freak who eats alone.
혼자 밥 먹는 여자가
꿈도 야물딱지셔
- 나야
- 왔어?
Sambuca margarita?
삼부카 마가리타?
It that a real thing?
그런 게 있었나?
Well, we only had sambuca,
so it is now.
삼부카 밖에 없어서
이런 게 나왔지
Listen, Joe. I need to I need
to talk to you about something.
- 실은 할 얘기가 있어
- 뭔데?
What's up?
It's about Kathy.
캐시 말인데
I like her.
난 캐시를 좋아해
사실 많이 좋아하지
I like her a lot, actually.
-You do?
-Yeah.
- 그래?
- 그래
Your timing couldn't be better.
타이밍 한번 절묘하다
이젠 남남이거든
She's not my girlfriend anymore.
What?
- 뭐?
- 우리 찢어졌다
-Yeah, she broke up with me.
-When?
저런... 언제?
Just now, after acting class.
오늘 연기수업 끝나고
I thought she was doing some scene,
so I let people watch.
연습인 줄 알았다가
공개적으로 쪽 팔았다
그거 정말 유감이다
너 괜찮냐?
Man, I am so sorry.
Are you okay?
I've been better, but I'm all right.
So you like her?
뭐 그런대로 견딜 만해
캐시가 좋다고?
Yes, but I don't have to.
- 하지만 안 될 말이지
- 아니... 난 괜찮아
No, it's okay.
- 그래?
- 그럼
You know why?
Because you came to me first.
왠지 알아?
나한테 먼저 말했으니까
I thought that would be
the best thing to do.
이게 최선이 아닌가 싶어
실망할까봐 말해두겠는데
내가 들은 바에 의하면
You might have your work
cut out for you.
When I talked to her, I got
the feeling she's into some other guy.
아무래도 다른 남자가
있는 것 같아
See, that's actually what
I wanted to talk to you about.
바로 그 얘기를 하고 싶었어
I think I know who the other guy is.
- 그 남자가 누군지 알아
- 누군데?
Who?
It's me.
- 나야, 내가 그 남자라고
- 뭐?
I'm the other guy.
What?
When you were late last night,
Kathy and I got to talking...
너 어제 늦게 들어왔잖아?
캐시랑 얘기하다가...
...and one thing led
to another, and....
어쩌다 보니...
And what?
Did you sleep with her?
- 그래서? 같이 잤어?
- 아냐, 키스만 했어
-No, I just kissed her.
-What? That's even worse!
뭐? 그게 더 심해
-How is that worse?
-It's the same!
- 뭐가 더 심해?
- 몰라, 그게 그거지
There's nothing I could do.
I think I'm in love with her!
미안하지만 어쩔 수 없었어
사랑하는데 어떡해
Who cares?
뭐가 됐든, 내 뒤통수를 쳐?
나라면 절대 그런 짓 못해
You went behind my back?
I'd never do that to you!
I have no excuses.
I was totally over the line.
맞아, 할말이 없다
선을 넘은 건 나니까
You're so far past the line,
that you can't even see the line!
선을 넘어?
이미 지나갔어
너한테는 선이 아니라
눈곱만한 점이었겠지
The line is a dot to you!
그렇지만 나도 견디기
힘들다는 것만 알아줘
Yes, right! And I feel horrible.
You have to believe me.
Oh, my God. Is that
why you bought all this stuff?
그래서 이딴 걸 사들였냐?
잘 들어둬
You know what?
I will not watch your TV.
네 TV는 절대 안 봐
네 오디오도 안 들어
I won't listen to your stereo.
And there's a loaf in the new
bread maker I won't eat. Know why?
새 제빵기에 든 계피 건포도
빵도 안 먹겠어, 왠지 알아?
-Probably because
-It's all tainted with your betrayal!
- 그야 뭐...
- 하나같이 배신의 흔적이니까
This apartment is empty to me!
I'm not happy about you either.
이제부터 여기는 빈집이야
너도 걸리적거려
And just so you know...
이거 아냐?
...I made that bread for you.
그 빵은 너 주려고 구웠다
Oh, my God! He's lost it.
He's totally lost it.
이런, 로스의 재능이
사라졌나 봐
What?
뭐?
피비, 이건 정말 최악이다
This cannot get any worse.
지하실의 쥐들도
목을 매달겠어
Rats in the basement
are hanging themselves.
Thank you. Thanks.
감사합니다
I lost it.
그래, 사라졌어
I won't play anymore.
난 그만할까 봐
마무리 좀 해줄래?
Would you?
Can you finish my set?
After that? Yeah.
못할 거 있나?
도움이 된다면야
No, I mean, if I can help.
Yeah, like I could lose it.
사라지긴 뭐가 사라져
What?
뭔데?
I played bad on purpose, guys.
일부러 엉터리 연주를 했지
Okay, you were trying to
play bad this whole time.
처음부터 엉터리로
나갔다 이거지?
아니, 방금 그 곡만
No. Just that last song.